<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jamie McQuire Research</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Jamie McQuire Research</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to add WiFi capabilities to your Arduino Nano BLE Sense board</title><link>https://example.com/blog/nano_ble_wifi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/nano_ble_wifi/</guid><description>Introduction The Arduino Nano BLE Sense development board is a powerful piece of kit with multiple sensors (accelerometer, microphone, humidity, &amp;hellip;) included - perfect for anyone wanting to start out in IoT development. Fitted with a nRF52840 [1] microcontroller, the development board boasts an ARM Cortex-M4 processor, enabling the deployment of machine learning models via TensorFlow Lite. Unfortunately, one of the downsides to this board is the lack of WiFi capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>https://example.com/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/</guid><description>Content [How to add WiFi capabilities to your Arduino Nano BLE Sense board:]https://example.com/blog/nano_ble_wifi/</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://example.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/contact/</guid><description> Academic Email: J.Mcquire2@newcastle.ac.uk Personal Email: jamiemcquire23@gmail.com Social Github</description></item><item><title>Jamie McQuire Research</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>About Me Computer Science PhD Researcher at Newcastle University investigating the design and implementation of decentralized analytic systems for wearable healthcare applications.
Research Summary My research investigates the design and implementation of next generation sensors and analytics systems for the analysis of wearable sensor data. I am investigating how federated learning systems can be designed to run at-scale using inexpensive, low-powered devices for the analysis of data generated from wearable devices.</description></item></channel></rss>